Translated By The Community Of WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com
Your Grace,
I want to say--
You will not speak.
How do I know you are
who you say you are?
If only I were otherwise.
If you are Tyrion Lannister,
why shouldn't I kill you
to pay your family back
for what it did to mine?
You want revenge
against the Lannisters?
I killed my mother
Joanna Lannister
on the day I was born.
I killed my father Tywin Lannister
with a bolt to the heart.
I am the greatest Lannister
killer of our time.
So I should welcome you
into my service
because you murdered members
of your own family?
Into your service?
Your Grace, we have
only just met.
It's too soon to know
if you deserve my service.
If you'd rather return
to the fighting pits,
just say the word.
When I was a young man,
I heard a story
about a baby born during the
worst storm in living memory.
She had no wealth,
no lands, no army,
only a name and a
handful of supporters,
most of whom probably thought they could
use that name to benefit themselves.
They kept her alive, moving
her from place to place,
often hours ahead of the men
who'd been sent to kill her.
She was eventually sold off to some
warlord on the edge of the world
and that appeared to be that.
And then a few years later,
the most well-informed
person I knew
told me that this girl without
wealth, lands, or armies
had somehow acquired all three
in a very short span of time,
along with three dragons.
He thought she was our best,
last chance to build
a better world.
I thought you were worth
meeting at the very least.
And why are you worth meeting?
Why should I spend
my time listening to you?
Because you cannot build
a better world on your own.
You have no one at your side who
understands the land you want to rule.
The strengths and
weaknesses of the houses
that will either
join or oppose you.
I will have a very large army
and very large dragons.
Killing and politics
aren't always the same thing.
When I served
as Hand of the King,
I did quite well with the latter
considering the king in question
preferred torturing animals
to leading his people.
I could do an even better job
advising a ruler worth the name.
If that is indeed what you are.
So you want to advise me?
Very well.
What would you
have me do with him?
I swore I would kill him
if he ever returned.
I know.
Why should the people trust a queen
who can't keep her promises?
Whomever Ser Jorah was when
he started informing on you,
he is no longer that man.
I can't remember
ever seeing a sane man
as devoted to anything
as he is to serving you.
He claims he would kill
for you and die for you
and nothing I ever witnessed
gives me reason to doubt him.
And yet he did betray you.
Did he have an opportunity
to confess his betrayal?
Yes.
Many opportunities.
And did he?
No, not until forced to do so.
He worships you.
He is in love with you, I think.
But he did not trust you
with the truth.
An unpleasant truth to be sure,
but one of great
significance to you.
He did not trust that you would
be wise enough to forgive him.
So I should kill him?
A ruler who kills
those devoted to her
is not a ruler
who inspires devotion.
And you're going to need
to inspire devotion,
a lot of it, if you're ever going
to rule across the Narrow Sea.
But you cannot have him
by your side when you do.
Remove Ser Jorah from the city.
Confess.
My son.
Let me speak to--
Confess.
I meant it.
My face will be the
last thing you see--
My name is Lanna.
I'm an orphan.
When I was eight,
I begged enough money
to buy my first
bucket of oysters.
I sold that bucket and made
enough money to buy two more.
It took a while, but
I finally saved enough
to buy myself an oyster cart.
Now every morning,
I make my way
down to the canals.
I pass the fish mongers
and the bakers.
I usually see Lhara,
my first customer of the day
on her way home.
Then I turn left
onto Moonsinger Lane--
Turn left onto Ragman Lane
where I do most of my trade.
Lanna is very impressive.
Very industrious.
She will make a fine servant
for the Many-Faced God.
How will she serve him?
She will no longer
turn left onto Ragman Lane.
She will turn right
and go to Ragman Harbor.
What will she do there?
She will see.
See what?
How can a man tell a girl this?
If he knew what she would see,
there would be
no reason to send her.
Oysters, clams, and cockles!
Your oysters fresh?
Best in the city.
You wouldn't lie
to an old man, would you?
Mm.
Very nice. Give me
four with vinegar.
It's my 18th voyage.
Returned from all of them
without a scratch on me.
Can't do it.
Please, I've three children.
Without me...
Here, take it.
You have to.
I've three children.
- What will they do?
- Come on.
They've nothing without me.
Please, you have to!
Please, you don't understand!
Please!
The man is a gambler.
He wages that a sailor's ship
will make it to its destination.
It is a strange wager
for the captain.
He only wins
if he loses his life.
So why would a captain make
the wager in the first place?
A girl tells a man
that she has seen.
If the captain dies,
the thin man pays
his family a lot of money.
But perhaps the gambler
loses his bet
and decides he does not
have to pay after all.
A destitute woman
and her small child,
what can they do to such a man if
he keeps their money for himself?
To whom can they turn
for recourse?
The Many-Faced God.
You said you didn't know
what I would see at the docks.
A man had no idea what a girl
would see and what she would not.
A girl named Lanna
will return to the docks.
She will watch the gambler.
She will come to know as much about
him as she knows about herself.
And then what?
A gift for the thin man.
She's not ready.
Perhaps she is,
perhaps she's not.
And if she's not?
It is all the same
to the Many-Faced God.
The trial will take place soon.
The High Sparrow
will be presenting
a substantial case against you.
The charges?
Fornication, treason, incest,
the murder of King Robert.
All lies.
Of course, Your Grace.
My concern is that
the Faith does not adhere
to the same standards
of proof as the crown.
I hope you'll excuse me
for saying it,
but belief is so often
the death of reason.
I wish you had said it sooner.
Is there any word from Jaime?
No, I'm afraid not.
Your Grace,
Grand Maester Pycelle
has summoned your Uncle Kevan
back from Casterly Rock
to serve as Hand of the King.
He now presides
over the small council.
Tell him I need to speak to him.
I implored him to visit
you, but he would not.
What about my son, the king?
If you can visit me,
then surely the king...
Your arrest and Queen
Margaery's arrest,
the king has not
taken them well.
He remains in his chambers.
His servants often find his food
in the hall left untouched.
You need to talk to him.
You need to talk to my son and
tell him to come and see me,
come and see his mother.
He-- I tried,
Your Grace.
He wouldn't see me.
He won't see anyone.
I can't stay here.
There is a way, Your Grace.
A way out.
Confess?
To the High Sparrow?
I won't.
I made him.
I rose him up from nothing.
I will not kneel before
some barefooted commoner
and beg his forgiveness.
Good-bye, my queen.
The work continues.
Why?
Why, Theon?
I'm not Theon.
There is no Theon.
- Reek.
Why did you tell him, Reek?
I was helping you.
You wanted to escape.
There is no escape.
Not ever.
Theon Greyjoy tried to escape.
The master knew.
He knows everything.
He hunted him and caught him
and strapped him to a cross
and cut away piece after piece
until there was no Theon left.
Good.
If it weren't for you,
I'd still have a family.
If I could do
what Ramsay did to you
right here, right now, I would.
I deserved everything.
I deserve to be Reek.
I did terrible things.
Turned on Robb.
Captured Winterfell.
- Killed those boys.
- They weren't "those boys."
They were Bran and Rickon.
They were your brothers.
You've known them
since they were born.
They weren't.
They were only--
Only what?
- I can't.
- Tell me.
I can't, not unless
the master says.
- Tell me. They weren't what?
- They weren't--
Tell me why Bran
and Rickon should be gone
while you still breathe the air.
Tell me to my face, Theon.
Tell me that they
weren't your brothers!
They weren't Bran and Rickon!
I couldn't find them.
It was two farm boys.
I killed them and burned
them so no one would know.
You didn't?
Do you know where they
went, Bran and Rickon?
I can't talk to you anymore.
Theon, you have to tell me.
Do you have any idea where--
Not Theon! Reek!
Our scouts tell us he's got
no more than 6,000 men.
More than half of those
are mounted, however.
And how high do
Stannis's horses jump?
Our walls have been
fully repaired.
The gates have been reinforced.
We have enough food
for six months.
We are more prepared for a
siege than they could ever be.
All we have to do is
wait for them to freeze,
starve, and mutiny.
You disagree?
Stannis isn't from the North.
You are, Father.
I think you're missing an opportunity
to show the people of the North
how House Bolton
treats southern invaders.
And what do you recommend?
That we not sit
and wait for Stannis
to decide what sort of
fight this is going to be.
That we hit first and hit hard
and leave a feast for the crows.
A smart commander does not
abandon a defensive advantage.
As long as we stay
behind these walls,
they can't touch us.
Not to mention
that the snow is so deep,
we couldn't get an army
through to engage them
even if we wanted to.
I don't need an army.
I need 20 good men.
So, have you decided yet?
Whether I'm worthy
of your service?
Have you decided yet whether
you're going to have me killed?
It's probably my safest option.
I can see why
you would think so.
It's what your father
would have done.
And what would
your father have done?
My father,
who publically
sentenced me to death?
I'd say his thoughts on having
me killed were abundantly clear.
Is that why you killed him?
Someday, if you decide
not to execute me,
I'll tell you all about
why I killed my father.
And on that day,
should it ever come,
we'll need more wine than this.
I know what my father was.
What he did.
I know the Mad King
earned his name.
So, here we sit.
Two terrible children
of two terrible fathers.
I'm terrible?
I've heard stories.
Why did you travel to the far side of
the world to meet someone terrible?
- To see if you were the right kind of terrible.
- Which kind is that?
The kind that prevents your
people from being even more so.
Well, I did reopen
the fighting pits.
Under my rule, murder will once
again become entertainment.
Yes, that was wise.
And you agreed to marry someone
you loathe for the greater good.
Very impressive.
My own sister married someone
she loathed as well,
though not by choice
and certainly not
for the greater good,
gods forbid.
She ended up having him killed.
Perhaps it won't come to that.
It's not impossible that Varys
was right about you after all.
Varys?
King Robert's spymaster?
Yes, he's the one who convinced
me to come find you.
He was my travelling companion
before Ser Jorah seized
that role for himself.
Jorah sent my secrets to Varys.
For 20 years the Spider oversaw
the campaign to find and kill me.
He did what he had
to do to survive.
He did a lot of other things as
well, things he didn't have to do.
I suspect he's the main reason you
weren't slaughtered in your crib.
But you trust him?
Yes, oddly.
He may be the only person
in the world I trust.
Except my brother.
The brother
who killed my father?
That's the one.
Perhaps I will have you
killed after all.
Your queenly prerogative.
I had given up on life
until Varys convinced me
you might be worth living for.
If you chop off my head, well,
my final days were interesting.
I'm not going to kill you.
No? Banish me?
No.
So if I'm not going
to be murdered
and I'm not going
to be banished--
You're going to advise me.
While you can still speak
in complete sentences.
Advise you on what?
How to get what I want.
The Iron Throne.
Perhaps you should try
wanting something else.
If I want jokes, I'll get
myself a proper fool.
I'm not entirely joking.
There's more to the world
than Westeros after all.
How many hundreds of thousands of lives
have you changed for the better here?
Perhaps this
is where you belong,
where you can do the most good.
I fought so that no child
born into Slaver's Bay
would ever know what it
meant to be bought or sold.
I will continue
that fight here and beyond.
But this is not my home.
When you get back to your
home, who supports you?
The common people.
Let's be generous and assume
that's going to happen.
Here in Slaver's Bay, you had the
support of the common people
and only the common people.
What was that like?
Ruling without the rich?
House Targaryen is gone.
Not a single person who shares your
blood is alive to support you.
The Starks are gone as well.
Our two terrible fathers
saw to that.
The remaining members
of House Lannister
will never back you, not ever.
Stannis Baratheon
won't back you, either.
His entire claim to the throne rests
on the illegitimacy of yours.
That leaves the Tyrells.
Not impossible, not enough.
Lannister, Targaryen,
Baratheon, Stark, Tyrell.
They're all just spokes
on a wheel.
This one's on top,
then that one's on top.
And on and on it spins,
crushing those on the ground.
It's a beautiful dream,
stopping the wheel.
You're not the first person
who's ever dreamt it.
I'm not going to stop the wheel.
I'm going to break the wheel.
You said whoever wins will fight at
the Great Pit in front of the queen.
I won.
- You struck me.
- Have me flogged if it makes you happy.
But I'm the best you've got.
If I win at the Great Pit,
how much can you sell me for?
You're a free man.
You could have gone anywhere.
Why did you come back?
Let me fight for her
and I belong to you.
Thirsty?
Confess.
I'll get out of here,
you realize, before long.
Confess.
I can make you a wealthy woman.
A lady of the court.
Confess.
Or I can make sure you die in the
most hideous way imaginable.
And all I do is sit here
imagining hideous ways
for you to die.
Does it hurt?
No.
Good.
How are you?
I'm not the one who got punched
and kicked in the face.
You know what I mean.
I'm good.
- Are you scared?
- A little.
Me, too.
- Who's there?
-  Olly.
Oh.
Come in.
I heard what happened.
Oh, not to worry.
Men brawl from time to time.
It's only natural.
Figured you were hungry.
Oh, you're a good lad.
Wanted to ask you something
if you've got the time.
I need to check on baby Sam.
Now then, how can I help?
- It's about the Lord Commander.
- Yes?
He's going up to Hardhome
to save all them wildlings.
Wildlings killed my mom and dad.
They killed everyone
in my village.
We've been
fighting them for years.
This wasn't a fight.
We were farmers
and they slaughtered us.
So why is he saving them?
Wildlings are people.
Just like us, there are
good ones and bad ones.
The one he's travelling with,
the one with the red beard,
he led the raid on my village.
-  Oh, Olly.
- How can he trust him?
I've seen the army of the dead.
I've seen the white walkers.
And they're coming for
us, for all the living.
And when it's time,
we'll need every
last man we can find.
But what if we let the
wildlings through the gates
and they cut our throats
while we sleep?
Jon's taking a risk,
but he has to.
We don't stand
a chance otherwise.
Sometimes a man
has to make hard choices,
choices that might look
wrong to others,
but you know are right
in the long run.
You believe that?
With all my heart.
Try not to worry, Olly.
I've been worrying
about Jon for years.
He always comes back.
Turn us about!
You trust me, Jon Snow?
Does that make me a fool?
We're fools together now.
Lord of Bones.
Been a long time.
Last time I saw you, the
little crow was your prisoner.
The other way around now.
What happened?
War.
War?
You call that a war?
The greatest army
the North has ever seen
cut to pieces
by some southern king.
We should gather the elders,
find somewhere quiet to talk.
You don't give the orders here.
I'm not giving an order.
Why aren't you in chains?
He's not my prisoner.
No?
What is he?
We're allies.
You fucking traitor.
You fight for the crows now?
I don't fight for the crows.
We're not here to fight.
We're here to talk.
Is that right?
You and the pretty crow
do a lot of talking, Tormund?
And when you're done talking,
do you get down on your
knees and suck his cock?
Gather the elders
and let's talk.
My name's Jon Snow.
I'm Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
We're not friends.
We've never been friends.
We won't become friends today.
This isn't about friendship.
This is about survival.
This is about putting
a 700-foot wall
between you
and what's out there.
You built that wall
to keep us out.
Since when do the crows
give two shits if we live?
In normal times we wouldn't.
But these aren't normal times.
The white walkers don't care
if a man's free folk or crow.
We're all the same to them,
meat for their army.
But together we can beat them.
Beat the white walkers?
Good luck with that.
Run from them, maybe.
It's not a trick.
It's a gift
for those who join us.
Dragonglass.
A man of the Night's Watch
used one of these daggers
to kill a walker.
- You saw this?
- No.
But I trust the man.
There are old stories
about dragonglass.
There are old stories about
ice spiders as big as hounds.
And with the things we've
seen, you don't believe them?
Come with me and
I'll share these weapons.
Come with you where?
There are good lands
south of the Wall.
The Night's Watch will let you
through the tunnel
and allow your people
to farm those lands.
I knew Mance Rayder.
He never wanted a war
with the Night's Watch.
He wanted a new life
for his people, for you.
We're prepared
to give you that new life.
If?
If you swear you'll join us
when the real war begins.
Where is Mance?
- He died.
- How?
I put an arrow
through his heart.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
I say we send the Lord Commander
back to Castle Black
with no eyes.
Hey, none of you saw Mance die.
I did.
The southern king who
broke our army, Stannis,
wanted to burn him alive
to send us a message.
Jon Snow defied
that cunt's orders.
His arrow was mercy.
What he did took courage.
And that's what we need today,
the courage to make peace
with men we've been
killing for generations.
I lost my father, my uncle,
and two brothers
fighting the damn crows.
I'm not asking you
to forget your dead.
I'll never forget mine.
I lost 50 brothers the night
that Mance attacked the Wall.
But I'm asking you
to think about
your children now.
They'll never have
children of their own
if we don't band together.
The Long Night is coming
and the dead come with it.
No clan can stop them.
The free folk can't stop them.
The Night's Watch
can't stop them.
And all the southern
kings can't stop them.
Only together, all of us.
And even then
it may not be enough,
but at least we'll give
the fuckers a fight.
You vouch for this man, Tormund?
He's prettier
than both my daughters,
but he knows how to fight.
He's young, but he
knows how to lead.
He didn't have
to come to Hardhome.
He came because he needs us
and we need him.
My ancestors would spit on me
if I broke bread with a crow.
So would mine, but fuck
'em, they're dead.
I'll never trust a man in black.
But I trust you, Tormund.
If you say this is the way,
we're with you.
This is the way.
I'm with Tormund.
We stay here, we're dead men.
At least with King Crow,
there's a chance.
Tormund.
Keep that new life
you want to give us.
And keep your glass, King Crow.
As soon as you get on his ships,
they're gonna slit your throats
and dump your bodies to the
bottom of the Shivering Sea.
That's our enemy.
That has always been our enemy.
I fucking hate Thenns.
- Move it.
- Be careful.
- Move 'em along, now.
- Cast-off time.
That's it, come on.
How many are with us?
5,000?
I'm not good at counting.
We're leaving too many behind.
The free folk are stubborn.
You know how long it took
Mance to band them together?
20 fucking years.
And he knew them better
than I ever will.
They're running out of food
and there's nothing to hunt.
They'll come around.
- Get yourselves ready.
- Aye!
Johnna is gonna look after you.
She's in charge.
You listen to her.
Take her. There you are.
I want to go with you.
I need to get the old
folks on the boats.
I'm right behind you.
I promise.
Go on.
Another one.
Keep moving.
We'll meet you out there.
Won't be able to take that on the boat.
It's too big.
-  That's the last one!
-  Three more! Move on!
There's more dragonglass everywhere.
I've got some more daggers
over here.
Put that dagger in his bag.
Uh...
Steady!
Shut the gates.
Close the gates!
Shut the gates!
Wait!
- Open the gate!
- Let us in!
Help us!
Please open it!
Open the gate!
Ready your arrows!
- Wait! Wait!
- Keep in line! Keep in line!
Get in line!
Get to the front!
Go on, shoot it!
- Wait, wait!
- Duncan, hold the line! Hold the line!
Lord Commander!
Get them to the ship
and come back for me!
- But you'll never make--
- Now!
- Let me on!
- Bloody fucking move!
- Let go!
You should be on
one of those boats.
So should you.
My little girls got on.
They're gonna let them pass the
Wall even if you're not there?
You have my word.
I've given orders.
Don't think you're gonna be
there to enforce those orders.
If they get through,
everyone dies.
Night's Watch, with me!
Move! Move!
Move!
No, no!
- Tormund, the sleigh!
- Okay, okay!
The dragonglass.
You and me, then!
Go!
Get the glass.
Come on!
The dragonglass.
Fuck the glass!
We are gonna die here!
Oh, fuck!
Tormund, run!
Wun Wun, to the sea.
Quickly!
-  Faster, faster!
-  Run, run!
Quickly!
- Quickly, row! Row!
- Go, go, come on!
Let's go!
Now, now!
Come on, row!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.MY-SUBS.com